Guide to the Alvin A. Achenbaum Papers, 1948-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Backer Spielvogel Bates, 1971-1995 and undated
  - Account Files
    - MTA (Metropolitan Transit Authority)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1992 and undated (Box BB10)
      - Financing Transportation in the New York Region (Regional Plan Association), 1992 (Box BB10)
      - Free Transit idea, 1992 and undated, (2 folders) (Box BB10)
      - Key questions and answers, undated (Box BB10)
      - MTA presentation, undated (Box BB10)
      - Printed materials, 1986-1993 (Box BB10)
    - Pfizer
      - Legal, 1990-1991 (Box BB10)
      - New market entries, 1990 (Box BB10)
      - New products, 1990-1991 (Box BB10)
      - Plax project, 1991 (Box BB10)
      - Role of Ethical Heritage in Product Success, undated (Box BB10)
      - Today's Marketing Needs, undated (Box BB10)
    - Philip Morris
      - American Consumer of the 1990s (James Morgan), 1992 (Box BB11)
      - Annual Report, 1990 (Box BB11)
      - Articles, 1991 (Box BB11)
      - Black and white private labels, 1992 (Box BB11)
      - Brand loyalty presentation, 1991 (Box BB11)
      - Brand share, 1992 (Box BB11)
      - Catalina marketing coupon solution, 1991 (Box BB11)
      - Cigarette brand share, 1990-1991 (Box BB11)
      - Cigarette pricing exploration, 1991 (Box BB11)
      - Clippings, 1974-1991 (Box BB11)
      - Consumer evaluation of Merit cigarettes, 1979 (Box BB11)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1991-1994 (Box BB11)
      - Coupon tracking report, undated (Box BB11)
      - Downsizing, 1991 (Box BB11)
      - Evaluating the Effectiveness of Price-Off Promotions in the Cigarette Market, 1983 (Box BB11)
      - Food study, 1992 and undated (Box BB11)
      - Legal (tobacco litigation cases), 1975-1984 (Box BB11)
      - Lifestyle study, 1992 (Box BB12)
      - Market share, 1990 (Box BB12)
      - Marketing information and analysis, 1990 (Box BB12)
      - Position paper on the value of brand names in the cigarette field, undated (Box BB12)
      - Price Elasticity in the Cigarette Market, 1991 (Box BB12)
      - Price Value Strategy Study, 1991 (Box BB12)
      - Pricing analysis, 1991 and undated (Box BB12)
      - Pricing data, 1986-1990 (Box BB12)
      - Pricing in the Cigarette Market, 1991, (2 folders) (Box BB12)
      - Pricing presentation, 1990-1991 and undated, (2 folders) (Box BB12)
      - Sales data, 1990-1991 (Box BB12)
      - Sales Promotion Evaluation Study, 1985 (Box BB13)
      - Study of Smokers' and Non-Smokers' Attitudes, 1990 (Box BB13)
    - Seagram
      - Captain Morgan presentation, 1994 (Box BB13)
      - Sales data, 1985-1990 (Box BB13)
      - Transformation of the Packaged Food and Beverage Marketing Environment and Its Impact on Marketing Communications, 1991 (Box BB13)
    - Sears
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1990-1993 (Box BB13)
      - Hudson's Department Store study, undated (Box BB13)
      - Service economy presentation, 1989-1992 (Box BB13)
      - Storyboards, 1991 (Box BB13)
    - Tropicana
      - Fruit beverages, 1992, (2 folders) (Box BB13)
    - Wendy's
      - Wendy's and Nutrition: A No-Compromise Solution, 1991 (Box BB13)
  - General Files
    - Advertising in a Recession, 1991 (Box BB14)
    - Advertising platform, undated (Box BB14)
    - Advertising process, 1992 and undated (Box BB14)
    - Advertising Strategy Made Easy (BSB Ltd), undated (Box BB14)
    - American Marketplace and Where It Is Headed in the Next 5 Years, 1990 (Box BB14)
    - Bates Builds Winning Brand Assets Worldwide (Larry Light), undated (Box BB14)
    - Battle of Brands (Larry Light), 1988 (Box BB14)
    - Bill Backer speech, undated (Box BB14)
    - Brand Communications Marketing Group, undated (Box BB14)
    - Brand Wheel, undated (Box BB14)
    - Branding (Larry Light), 1988 (Box BB14)
    - Branding in the New Marketing Environment, 1991, (2 folders) (Box BB14)
    - Branding paper, 1990 and undated (Box BB14)
    - Break Through (BSB Canada newsletter), circa 1990 (Box BB14)
    - BSB Projections: 2002, 1993 (Box BB14)
    - BSB Resources, undated (Box BB14)
    - BSB Strategy Book (Hong Kong Office), undated (Box BB15)
    - Building Brands in the Nineties (George Patterson Advertising, Sydney), undated (Box BB15)
    - Challenge of Managing Brand Equity in a Changing Marketplace, undated (Box BB15)
    - Changing World of Retail, 1992 (Box BB15)
    - Chronological memos, 1990 Jan.-1991 May, (4 folders) (Box BB15)
    - Chronological memos, 1989 Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box BB16)
    - Clippings, 1977-1993, (2 folders) (Box BB16)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1984-1992 (Box BB16)
    - Currents (newsletter), 1991-1993 (Box BB16)
    - Discussion notes for a meeting with B. Nicholson and T. Campbell, 1990 (Box BB16)
    - Economic Theory and the Idea of Marketing Productivity (Robert Steiner), 1974 (Box BB16)
    - Enhancing Advertising Productivity, 1992 (Box BB16)
    - Forecasting, undated (Box BB16)
    - How Should the Brand Management System Be Modified to Adapt to the New Marketing Environment?, 1990 (Box BB16)
    - How to Change Advertising Agencies, 1971-1974 (Box BB17)
    - Marketing communications process, undated (Box BB17)
    - Mission: Nurturing Brand Equity, undated (Box BB17)
    - New business program, 1990 (Box BB17)
    - New Perspective for BSBW, 1990 (Box BB17)
    - New products/new markets, 1987-1991 and undated (Box BB17)
    - Obtaining New Business, 1991, (2 folders) (Box BB17)
    - Planning for ROI (Dr. Ruth Ziff), undated (Box BB17)
    - Presentation, 1990, (2 folders) (Box BB17)
    - Process/Start Work Brief, final version, 1992 (Box BB17)
    - Promo magazine, 1990 (Box BB17)
    - Services, miscellaneous, 1990-1993 and undated (Box BB17)
    - Slides, undated, (5 folders) (Box BB18)
    - Strategies for Addressing the New Market Environment, 1988 (Box BB18)
    - Ten Cardinal Sins in New Business Solicitation, 1990, (3 folders) (Box BB18)
    - That Which We Call a Rose, By Any Other Name, Might Not Smell As Sweet, undated (Box BB19)
    - These Prices Are Killing Us!, 1993 and undated (Box BB19)
    - Transformation of the Packaged Food and Beverage Marketing Environment and Its Impact on Marketing Communications, 1990-1991 (Box BB19)
    - White paper topics, undated (Box BB19)
    - Will the Advertising Agency Business Be Materially Different in the Next 5 or 6 Years?, undated (Box BB19)
    - Will the Advertising/Marketing Communications Agency Business Be Materially Different in the Next 5 or 6 Years?, undated (Box BB19)
- Canter Achenbaum Associates (Includes Canter Achenbaum Heekin), 1960-2004 and undated
  - Account Files
    - Alfred Dunhill
      - Long-term marketing plan, 1983 (Box CA1)
      - Marketing planning, 1983 (Box CA1)
    - American Express
      - Establishing a Marketing Services Unit, 1985 (Box CA1)
    - Ameritech/Wisconsin Bell
      - Compensation proposal, 1989 (Box CA1)
    - AMI (American Medical International)
      - Marketing at AMI, 1983 (Box CA1)
      - Presentations, 1984, (3 folders) (Box CA1)
    - Anheuser-Busch
      - Compensation feasibility study, 1986 (Box CA1)
    - AT&T
      - Agency compensation arrangement, 1989 (Box CA2)
      - Agency compensation review, 1989 (Box CA2)
      - Contracts, 1982-1986, (2 folders) (Box CA2)
      - Presentation, undated (Box CA2)
      - Pro forma, correspondence, 1989 (Box CA2)
      - Proposal to Assess and Modify AT&T's Compensation Arrangements with Its Advertising Agencies, 1989 (Box CA2)
    - Avis
      - Assessment of Avis Marketing Department Organization, 1987 (Box CA2)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1987 (Box CA2)
      - Marketing Department organization recommendation, draft, 1987 (Box CA2)
      - Marketing Department organization recommendation, final, 1987 (Box CA3)
    - Backer Spielvogel Bates
      - Obtaining New Accounts, 1988, (2 folders) (Box CA3)
    - Bank of New York
      - Situation analysis, 1979, (2 folders) (Box CA3)
    - Best Foods
      - New product market selection, 1977 (Box CA3)
      - New product strategy, 1977 (Box CA3)
      - Pizza spread recommendation, 1977 (Box CA3)
    - Blendax
      - Review of toiletry/cosmetic joint venture candidates, 1978 (Box CA3)
    - Bloom Agency
      - Target Identification Study, 1977 (Box CA3)
    - BMW
      - Agency compensation, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box CA4)
    - Carter-Wallace
      - Research review of aerosol shaving cream market, 1975 (Box CA4)
    - Champion Valley Farms
      - Review of commercial dog food market, 1977 (Box CA4)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank
      - Assessment of compensation arrangement, 1982 (Box CA4)
    - Chrysler
      - Agency compensation review, 1982 (Box CA4)
      - Agency selection, 1982 and undated (Box CA4)
      - Agreement with BBDO, 1983, (2 folders) (Box CA4)
      - Assessment of Kenyon & Eckhardt/Chrysler agency compensation arrangement, 1983 (Box CA4)
      - BBDO meeting on agency compensation, 1982 (Box CA4)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1983-1987 (Box CA4)
      - Media project, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box CA5)
      - Proposal for development of a marketing program, 1979 (Box CA5)
    - Citicorp
      - Assessment of the future market for home Videotex systems, 1986 (Box CA5)
      - CSI marketing overview, 1980 (Box CA5)
      - Home Videotex systems, 1986 (Box CA5)
      - Proposal for Merchant Banking Group, 1982 (Box CA5)
      - Study of Citicorp International Group's identity, 1982 (Box CA5)
    - Clairol
      - Enhancing Agency Performance, circa 1976 (Box CA5)
      - Meeting, 1976 (Box CA5)
    - CPC International
      - Situation analysis of the snack market, 1977 (Box CA5)
      - Situation analysis of the spread market, 1977 (Box CA5)
    - CVS
      - Advertising agency selection,1989 (Box CA6)
      - Agency selection, 1989 (Box CA6)
      - Compensation agreement, 1989 (Box CA6)
      - Meeting book, 1989 (Box CA6)
    - D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles
      - The Business of Acquiring New Business, 1985 (Box CA6)
    - Dentsu
      - Advertising Agency Business in the United States, 1989 (Box CA6)
      - Appropriateness of Acquiring U.S. Advertising Agencies, 1989 (Box CA6)
      - Assessment of Advertising Agency Mega-Mergers, 1986 (Box CA6)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box CA7)
      - Management Policies of the Top-Ranked Advertising Agencies in the U.S., 1985 (Box CA7)
      - Organization of Large Agencies, 1983-1985, (2 folders) (Box CA7)
      - Presentation on Project H, 1989 (Box CA7)
      - Project H Phase One, 1989 (Box CA7)
    - Department of the Army
      - Assessment of Army recruitment advertising, 1986 (Box CA7)
      - Audit of Army recruitment advertising, 1986, (1 of 2 folders) (Box CA7)
      - Audit of Army recruitment advertising, 1986, (2 of 2 folders) (Box CA8)
      - Proposal for audit, 1985 (Box CA8)
    - Dukakis campaign
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box CA8)
    - Federal Trade Commission
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous (Re: research findings/claims in advertisements), 1974, (2 folders) (Box CA8)
    - Fisher-Price
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1982-1990 (Box CA8)
      - Evaluation of expansion opportunities, 1982 (Box CA8)
      - Marketing assessment, 1982, (2 folders) (Box CA8)
    - Ford
      - Agency relations study, undated, (2 folders) (Box CA9)
      - Sales and compensation data (ITC report), 1960-1985, (3 folders) (Box CA9)
    - Franzia Wine
      - Review of the premium jug wine marketing program, 1977 (Box CA9)
    - General Electric
      - Agency compensation assessment, 1986, (2 folders) (Box CA10)
      - Agency compensation review, 1986 (Box CA10)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1989 (Box CA10)
      - Pro forma contract, 1987 (Box CA10)
    - General Foods
      - Analysis of the gelatin market, 1976 (Box CA10)
      - Assessment of marketing image, 1986 (Box CA10)
      - Cool Whip price/promotion analysis, 1986 (Box CA10)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box CA10)
      - Evaluation of Price Promotions in the Whipped Topping Market, 1986 (Box CA10)
      - Jell-O Gelatin marketing strategy, 1976 (Box CA10)
      - Marketing Food Products, 1988 (Box CA10)
      - Marketing Plan for Jell-O, 1976 (Box CA10)
      - Marketing position paper on the gelatin market, 1976 (Box CA10)
      - Push marketing, 1985 (Box CA10)
      - Sales promotion, 1985 (Box CA11)
      - Speech materials, 1987-1989 (Box CA11)
    - Gillette
      - Proposals for changing agency compensation arrangements, 1980, (3 folders) (Box CA11)
      - Review of agency compensation, 1979 (Box CA11)
    - H&R Block
      - Market test program, 1976, 1982 (Box CA11)
      - Marketing programs, 1979 (Box CA11)
      - Media plan, 1981 (Box CA11)
      - New Service Opportunity, 1978 (Box CA12)
    - Hallmark
      - Agency selection, undated (Box CA12)
      - Assessment of standing in the greeting card market, 1984 (Box CA12)
      - Compensation, 1984 (Box CA12)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box CA12)
      - Legal case with Blue Mountain, 1988 (Box CA12)
      - Management meeting, 1988 (Box CA12)
      - Media test, 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box CA12)
      - Meeting book, 1988 (Box CA12)
      - Research Proposal on Marketing Strategies to Expand the Greeting Card Business, 1980 (Box CA12)
      - Study of market opportunities, 1981 (Box CA13)
      - Way for Increasing Summer Sales, 1980 (Box CA13)
    - Hattori
      - Agency compensation, 1987 (Box CA13)
    - Heublein
      - Assessment of new product development, 1983 (Box CA13)
    - H.J. Heinz
      - Maximizing Advertising Agency Productivity, 1981 (Box CA13)
    - Honda
      - Agency/client agreement (Ketchum), 1986 (Box CA13)
      - Compensation review, 1985 (Box CA13)
      - Honda/Reuben Postaer compensation assessment, 1987 (Box CA13)
      - Pro forma agreement (Ketchum), 1985 (Box CA13)
      - Review of Professional and Financial Partnership, 1987 (Box CA13)
    - Illinois Bell
      - Agency compensation proposal, 1989 (Box CA13)
    - Johnson & Johnson
      - Electrolytic/Isotonic drink market, 1976 (Box CA13)
    - J.P. Morgan
      - Account review, undated (Box CA13)
      - Agency selection, 1989 (Box CA14)
      - Compensation agreement, 1989 (Box CA14)
      - Meeting book, 1989, (2 folders) (Box CA14)
    - Kal-Kan
      - Agency compensation review, 1989 (Box CA14)
      - Assessment of compensation arrangement, 1989 (Box CA14)
      - Compensation agreement, 1989 (Box CA14)
      - Pedigree action plan, 1989 (Box CA14)
      - Sheba action plan, 1989 (Box CA14)
      - Whiskas action plan, 1989 (Box CA14)
    - Lexus
      - Agency agreement, undated (Box CA14)
    - Lorimar
      - Agency acquisition analysis, 1984 (Box CA14)
      - Agency acquisition proposed strategy, 1984 (Box CA15)
      - Acquisition--answers to selected questions, 1985 (Box CA15)
      - Bozell & Jacobs, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box CA15)
      - Kenyon & Eckhardt, 1983-1984 (Box CA15)
      - Rosenfeld, Sirowite & Lawson, 1984 (Box CA15)
    - Magnavox
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box CA15)
      - Pricing reports, 1973-1974 (Box CA15)
      - Program for Achieving Magnavox Color TV Set Objectives, 1975 (Box CA15)
      - Sales force study, undated (Box CA15)
      - Study of Magnavox pricing, 1974 (Box CA16)
    - Mazda
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1988 and undated (Box CA16)
      - Mazda/FCB agency compensation, 1988 (Box CA16)
      - Presentation guide for FCB Advertising Challenge teams, 1988 (Box CA16)
      - Project concerned with advertiser/agency relationship, 1987 (Box CA16)
    - MGM/UA
      - Potential Market for Motion Picture Videocassette Advertising, 1987 (Box CA16)
      - Using Videocassettes as a Marketing Tool, 1988 (Box CA16)
    - Minolta
      - Agency agreements, 1982 (Box CA16)
      - Agency competition, undated, (1 of 3 folders) (Box CA16)
      - Agency competition, undated, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box CA17)
      - Assessment of compensation arrangement, 1980 (Box CA17)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1981 and undated (Box CA17)
      - Long-term marketing plan, 1979-1980 (Box CA17)
      - Recommended compensation system, 1980 (Box CA17)
    - Mogen David
      - California Wine Market, 1980, (1 of 4 folders) (Box CA17)
      - California Wine Market, 1980, (2-4 of 4 folders) (Box CA18)
      - Supplementary analyses, 1980 (Box CA18)
    - Morse Shoe Co.
      - Fayva Division compensation arrangement, 1985 (Box CA18)
    - Mutual of Omaha
      - Analysis of Management of Advertising Process, 1979 (Box CA18)
    - NBC
      - Proposal for Evaluating Television Pricing, 1975 (Box CA18)
    - Needham Harper & Steers
      - Report on the Michelin Tire Corporation, 1981 (Box CA18)
    - Nestlé
      - Achenbaum speech--Managing Your Advertising, 1990 (Box CA18)
      - Annual Report, 1989 (Box CA18)
      - Clippings, 1982-2004, (2 folders) (Box CA18)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1987-1990 (Box CA19)
      - C. Pagamo concluding remarks, 1989 (Box CA19)
      - Management Communications Conference, 1987-1990, (1-6 of 7 folders) (Box CA19)
      - Management Communications Conference, 1987-1990, (7 of 7 folders) (Box CA20)
      - Nestlé--A Long Adventure 1866-1986, 1986 (Box CA20)
      - Presentation on leadership, undated (Box CA20)
      - Presentation on trade marketing, undated (Box CA20)
      - Seminar on marketing communications, 1987 (Box CA20)
    - New England Apple Products (Veryfine)
      - Compensation agreement, 1989 (Box CA20)
      - Compensation assessment, 1989 (Box CA20)
    - New York Racing Association
      - Evaluation of NYRA Sales Promotion Agency, 1987 (Box CA20)
    - Nissan
      - General Files
        - Advertising Agency Compensation Study, 1976 (Box CA20)
        - Agency agreements, 1975-1977 (Box CA20)
        - Agency compensation arrangement, 1977 (Box CA20)
        - Agency evaluation, 1987 (Box CA20)
        - Agency search, 1987, (2 folders) (Box CA21)
        - Agency selection, 1977, (2 folders) (Box CA21)
        - Agency selection--Operation Ted Williams, undated, (2 folders) (Box CA21)
        - Assessment of Nissan Advertising Media Plan, 1983-1984, (4 folders) (Box CA22)
        - Clippings, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box CA22)
        - Compensation, 1987-1988 (Box CA22)
        - Decision support system, 1984 (Box CA22)
        - Market profiles, 1985-1987 (Box CA23)
        - Media expenditures, 1985 (Box CA23)
        - Precise Market Potentials for Geographically Allocating Marketing Efforts, 1976 (Box CA23)
      - Horizon project (Infiniti launch)
        - Clippings, 1987, (2 folders) (Box CA23)
        - Competitive placement, 1987 (Box CA23)
        - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1987, (3 folders) (Box CA23)
        - Final presentation, 1987 (Box CA23)
        - Infiniti press conference, 1987 (Box CA23)
        - Japanese image position paper (Timothy O'Shea), 1987 (Box CA23)
        - Meeting notes, 1987 (Box CA24)
        - Miscellaneous notes and reports, 1983-1987 (Box CA24)
        - Nomenclature/naming, 1987 (Box CA24)
        - Outline and interview notes, 1987 (Box CA24)
        - Phase 1 presentation, 1987 (Box CA24)
        - Phase 2 recommendations, 1987 (Box CA24)
        - Planning, 1987 (Box CA24)
        - Preliminary media program, 1987 (Box CA24)
        - Presentation materials and proposals, 1987 (Box CA25)
        - Research
          - Buying incentive, 1986-1987 (Box CA25)
          - Forecasts, 1987 (Box CA25)
          - Industry forecasts, 1986-1987 (Box CA25)
          - Miscellaneous notes and reports, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box CA25)
          - Nissan position papers, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box CA25)
          - Surveys, 1986 (Box CA25)
        - Sales data, 1986-1987, (1 of 2 folders) (Box CA25)
        - Sales data, 1986-1987, (2 of 2 folders) (Box CA26)
        - Toyama meeting, undated (Box CA26)
      - Research
        - Brand image, 1986 (Box CA26)
        - Car quality, 1986 (Box CA26)
        - Computer market models, 1985 (Box CA26)
        - Demographics, 1984-1987 (Box CA26)
        - Miscellaneous notes and reports, 1987 (Box CA26)
        - Surveys, 1985-1986 (Box CA26)
        - VALS (Values and Lifestyles) typologies, 1987 (Box CA26)
        - Sales and forecasts, 1987 (Box CA26)
    - Office of the Secretary of Defense
      - Audits
        - Active Army and Army Reserve Recruitment Advertising Management, 1979 (Box CA26)
        - Air Force Recruitment Advertising Management, 1979 (Box CA26)
        - Army ROTC Recruitment Advertising Management, 1979 (Box CA26)
        - U.S. Armed Services Recruitment Advertising Management, 1979 (Box CA26)
        - U.S. Armed Services Vol. 1a, Active Army, 1979 (Box CA27)
        - U.S. Armed Services Vol. 1b, Army Reserve, 1979 (Box CA27)
        - U.S. Armed Services Vol. 1c, Army ROTC, 1979 (Box CA27)
        - U.S. Armed Services Vol. 2, Navy, 1979 (Box CA27)
        - U.S. Armed Services Vol. 3, Marine Corps, 1979 (Box CA27)
        - U.S. Armed Services Vol. 4, Air Force, 1979 (Box CA27)
        - U.S. Armed Services Vol. 5, National Guard, 1979 (Box CA27)
        - U.S. Armed Services Vol. 6, Contractor and Subcontractor Remuneration and Billing, 1980 (Box CA28)
        - U.S. Armed Services Vol. 7, Comparisons, 1979 (Box CA28)
        - Management Summary of Advertising Issues (Navy), 1979 (Box CA28)
        - Presentation to Marine Corps, 1979 (Box CA28)
      - Proposals
        - Assess Performance of Navy Recruitment Advertising, 1986 (Box CA28)
        - Audit of Army recruitment advertising, 1985 (Box CA28)
        - Develop Common Advertising Pretesting Methods, 1979 (Box CA28)
        - In-Market Recruitment Advertising Mix Test, 1982 (Box CA28)
        - Management Audit of DoD Recruitment Advertising, 1978 (Box CA28)
        - Technical Review of N.W. Ayer Advertising Effectiveness Model, 1979 (Box CA28)
        - Proposed Joint vs. Service-Specific Advertising Resource Mix Test, 1983 (Box CA28)
        - Recommendations for Improving Armed Services Procedures for Selecting and Compensating Advertising Agencies, 1981, (1 of 2 folders) (Box CA28)
        - Recommendations for Improving Armed Services Procedures for Selecting and Compensating Advertising Agencies, 1981, (2 of 2 folders) (Box CA29)
        - Statement of work, 1983 (Box CA29)
    - Ogilvy & Mather
      - Obtaining New Accounts, 1988 (Box CA29)
      - Obtaining New Business, 1989 (Box CA29)
    - Owens-Corning
      - Builder Research on Selected Home Building Projects, 1974 (Box CA29)
      - Building conversion study, 1982 (Box CA29)
      - Continuing Research Program for Owens-Corning Fiberglass, 1975 (Box CA29)
      - Estimating Total Demand for Building Insulation, 1975 (Box CA29)
      - Market Audit of the Mechanical Division, 1978 (Box CA29)
      - Program for Tracking Demand for Light Density Insulation, 1974 (Box CA30)
      - Study of the Use of Insulation in New Residential Construction, 1974 (Box CA30)
      - Survey of insulation contractors, 1977 (Box CA30)
      - Technical Appendix, 1974 (Box CA30)
    - PCA International Acquisition Company
      - Business plan, 1986 (Box CA30)
      - Color portrait market, 1986 (Box CA30)
      - Corporate/background information, 1982-1986 (Box CA30)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box CA30)
      - Customer acquisition, 1985 (Box CA30)
      - Marketing plans, 1982-1985, (3 folders) (Box CA31)
      - Media test, 1983 (Box CA31)
      - Operations, 1985 (Box CA31)
      - PCA and Foote Cone Belding, 1982 (Box CA31)
      - Preferred Customer Program, 1985, (2 folders) (Box CA31)